healthyleo.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy - HealthyLeo.com

**Privacy Policy for https://healthyleo.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, feel free to contact us by email at info@healthyleo.com

At https://healthyleo.com/, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal data that is received and collected by the partners of https://healthyleo.com and how it is used.  
**https://healthyleo.com does not collect or store personal data about any of it’s visitors.**

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, https://healthyleo.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies**

The following partners of https://healthyleo.com collect and use personal data (in the form of cookies and personal identifiers) to personalize web experiences and offer more relevant ads:

– **Google Adsense** , as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on https://healthyleo.com/.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>

-Google Analytics. https://support.google.com/analytics/topic/2919631?hl=en&ref_topic=1008008

-Sulvo. https://sulvo.com/privacy.html

-Taboola. https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy

-Content Ignite – Think Clever Media Ltd. https://www.contentignite.com/privacy-policy/

-Revcontent. https://faq.revcontent.com/customer/en/portal/articles/2703838-revcontent-s-privacy-and-cookie-policy

-Underdog Media. https://underdogmedia.com/privacy-policy/

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on https://healthyleo.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

https://healthyleo.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. https://healthyleo.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
